(Sun Honglei)
(Li Naiwen)
(Guo Jingfei)
(Liu Yuning)
(Gong Jun)
(Chen Xingxu)
(Wang Yuwen)
(Lin Yi)
=Wow The World S2 Recap Special=
(Ongoing concern)
Sweating from the pain.
My kidney hurts.
Your kidney hurts?
Where's the kidney, Naiwen?
(Risk my kidneys for you)
I can't stand you.
(Doesn't hurt anymore?)
I really can't stand you.
He's even playing along.
No. He asked me with genuine concern.
I could just
play along.
Did you figure it out?
You didn't?
Not at all?
His kidney hurts.
What?
I think your version
of "Love Till Death"
sounds better than your usual take.
How did you know
I was going to sing "Love Till Death"?
We...
Did you hear that just now?
So you were outside
and heard it, right?
You just found out?
Did he just find out?
What do you mean?
We're...
Everything is fake.
What?
So what is real?
Why are you so cute?
(So cute that I can't bear
to lie to you)
Then tell me,
what is real?
This looks really good on you.
(Suit Squad)
(Grand finale drop)
Didn't they change?
Only I changed?
(Memory wipe)
Why are you wearing this?
Why are you dressed like that?
What do you mean?
Bad Lei.
- A streetwear brand.
- What is Bad Lei?
- What does Bad Lei mean?
What does Bad Lei mean?
It looks pretty nice.
Honglei's brand.
(Speak up for me)
I don't know.
This is Honglei's streetwear brand.
What?
- How could Lei have a streetwear brand?
- Yeah, how's that possible?
(Hanging on)
Lei.
Did you forget? You just said it.
Bad Lei.
What's wrong with you?
When did I say that?
Bad Lei. Look here.
(Here is the evidence)
Bad Lei.
- Hahahaha.
- Bad Lei.
Could I have
(Blood-kin test, now)
written this myself?
(Voice crack)
Honglei, your name is right here.
(Trapped in the self-proof loop)
When did I say that?
What?
(Completely broken)
This...
Get this footage for me.
(Footage won't go bad)
We have the footage here.
At such a young age,
why do you like
such flashy clothes?
Right.
Well...
Is this part not over yet?
(You're about to cry out of frustration)
Tell me, what is real?
(You win)
Okay.
(So loud, So intense)
I think Honglei
is definitely going to be carried out.
Because when he was young,
he often did this kind of thing.
I think that's the case.
(Yuning, one more line)
For the variety show effect,
we might have to carry him out.
(Just an excuse)
(Waiting for me here)
(Jun agrees)
Let's get Honglei out first.
Lin Yi, get off this chair.
(Overcoming all obstacles)
You get off this chair first.
(Locked in)
You can't abandon me.
- I won't abandon you.
- You hear that?
I won't abandon you.
The two of us
will stick together forever.
We will stick together forever.
Yuning, your idea is very good.
(Off-court guidance)
No matter what, carry him out.
Then let's carry
both of them out together.
Think about it this way. Hold on.
Wait a second.
Come on.
- One, two, three.
No.
(Mouth muscles tensing)
Wait.
Wait a second.
(Strength running out)
(Everyone exhausted)
It's almost as draining
as bungee jumping.
So Lin Yi, you get up first.
Lin Yi.
(Locked again)
Lin Yi, get up.
Too heavy.
If you get up,
it'll be easier for us to carry him.
Yi.
(Tightly locked)
Lin Yi, how can you trust him?
Just push him away
rudely.
Lin Yi.
(Honglei clinging to me)
Just
pull him apart like that.
(Is it that hard to pull him apart?)
Carrying him might be easier.
Just
pull him apart.
Run.
Run, Lin Yi. Trust me.
Carry him.
Hold him up.
(Who? What? How?)
- Go.
Lift that side up.
(How to help exactly?)
Let him leave with some dignity.
Give me a slow-motion shot.
(Here is the slow-motion shot)
(Get out of here)
(The second one gets carried out)
Liu Yuning.
You're such a bad guy.
(Full support)
Get her out first.
One by one.
Lin Yi.
No.
Then you two get out together.
You two get out together.
Only one counts.
Lin Yi came out first.
So I'm the clown.
(Finally realized)
He's been up to mischief.
Jun.
While you two still have energy,
carry him out.
No. If I get taken out,
it'll just be the two of you left.
- So what?
No difference.
We can play rock-paper-scissors.
Listen, here's the thing.
It's okay. You guys talk.
Can't stir things up anymore.
I'm not a threat to them,
because they...
Definitely.
You are a threat in height.
And also a threat in looks.
- And also a threat in looks.
- Definitely a threat in looks.
I admit it.
(What more is there to say?)
I admit that.
The most handsome person
in this room gets out.
Definitely a threat in looks.
Okay, no problem.
(Trigger keyword: Handsome)
I can walk out by myself.
As long as this keyword gets mentioned,
I'm leaving right away.
You're so handsome and gorgeous.
You two...
(Brain offline)
Really handsome.
So good-looking.
If you don't go out, who will?
You're so good-looking. You get out.
You're so handsome and gorgeous.
Really handsome.
Go out with dignity.
I'll lend you my glasses.
You're so handsome. Get going.
Slow-motion shot, everyone.
Liu Yuning is the most handsome.
- Liu Yuning is the most handsome.
(Who can resist this?)
Liu Yuning is the most handsome.
- Liu Yuning is the most handsome.
Liu Yuning.
(Liu Yuning is the most handsome)
Turn around.
To the right.
(Li Naiwen out)
Out.
Nai.
The village kids in the south bully me
for my old age and weakness.
Are eliminations based on age?
(Fate is playing tricks
on the big brother)
Then you're in danger, Fei.
(Big brother, Second brother,
Third brother)
I'm up next.
The pressure surges all of a sudden.
(Never compromise with age)
To the left.
(So sudden)
I'm up next.
As expected.
What you say comes true.
(In that case)
Who's next?
Is it my turn?
It's going by age.
I just refuse to admit I'm old.
I won't admit it.
(Bound to break the age curse)
You must break this curse.
That's right.
Let's go.
Turn around.
(Focused)
(Keep an eye on fourth brother's fate)
Turn around.
To the left.
(Bro, you're going the opposite way)
What you say comes true.
Bro.
(Liu Yuning out)
You must break this curse.
That's right.
Is this a curse?
Isn't it my turn now?
(Exactly the same)
Is it my turn?
Okay.
Fight for our age.
(It's fifth brother's time to fire up)
Jun.
Go for it.
Fight for our age.
Okay.
Three, two, one.
Turn around.
(Eyes on him)
(What are you doing?)
(Gong Jun out)
You...
It really is you.
What you say comes true.
- Oh my God.
I really forgot.
You came and grabbed mine.
Who's next?
I'm up next.
(Sixth brother is panicking)
(So scared)
You can't go against the order.
No one can escape.
(Can this curse be broken?)
(It's sixth brother's time to fire up)
(Only practice hard)
To the left. To the right.
Three, two, one.
Turn around.
To the right.
(Zhou Ye out)
(I did it)
This...
Not this time.
Start.
(Moving boldly)
(Falling right into my lap?)
(Then I won't hold back)
Lin Yi is moving, right?
Lin Yi.
Lin Yi is moving.
Who just hit me twice?
(Guiding them right away)
Lin Yi, why are you moving?
(Suspicious)
Why are you moving?
Lin Yi, why are you running so fast?
Lin Yi.
(Instant performance)
It's definitely Lin Yi.
Lin Yi moved.
Lin Yi.
Lin Yi is one of them.
(Feeling wronged)
I'm going to fight back.
Don't move.
Who is it?
(Go away! I'll hit you! Stay back! Let me go)
(Stay calm)
It's me, Naiwen.
It's me.
(Calm him down)
I'm here.
- I'm Lin Yi.
- Okay.
Isn't this...
Lin Yi.
Right, it's Lin Yi.
Definitely him.
Lin Yi, right?
I'm right here.
I didn't move.
(Wronged)
Were you trying to hit me earlier?
No, I didn't.
Then don't move.
I won't move.
Lin Yi.
(Great chance)
I'm here.
Where are you?
(Well-behaved)
Control one more.
(Demon Pill strikes)
Naiwen.
It wasn't me.
(Trust crumbled)
Naiwen.
- Who is it?
- It wasn't me.
You.
It really wasn't me.
It wasn't me.
What happened?
Naiwen.
It wasn't me.
You're too ruthless.
Who?
He pretended to control me,
and hit me twice with his left hand.
It wasn't me.
(Weak, helpless, and getting hit)
The older, the wiser.
(Pretty Sheep making a move)
Find the clothes.
Find the clothes first.
The clothes.
(Your delivery, please check)
(Picking up supplies)
(50-year-old Pretty Sheep in mid-air,
struggling to take off shoes)
Shoes. Put on the shoes first.
Put on the shoes first.
- Shoes. Put on the shoes first.
- Bub.
Put on the shoes first.
Hey.
♪The wolf falls in love with the sheep♪
- ♪Crazy in love♪
(Fall)
♪Crazy in love♪
(The path under the elbow
is Gong Jun's leg)
(Are you still going home for dinner?
No)
You can't.
♪The wolf falls in love with the sheep♪
Ah.
(Tossed out of the arena)
Can he get out?
Did they all see it?
(Grabbing in one go)
Chen Xingxu.
(Betrayed by the sweater,
Chen Xingxu turned into a wolf)
Move.
Let's go.
- Run.
- Chen Xingxu.
Pick Nai up.
Quick.
(Don't dare to move)
(Pitch-black white socks)
(A man needs to keep his dignity)
My pants.
(Lifting the sedan)
Come on.
My pants.
Forward.
(Please handle fifty-year-old Pretty Sheep gently)
I'm badly hurt from the fall.
My shoes.
(Not going home for dinner)
Stop.
♪The wolf♪
♪Falls in love with the sheep♪
(Come here quickly)
(Protecting)
- ♪Crazy in love♪ - ♪Crazy in love♪
(Shielding with the body)
Did you catch him?
Lin Yi.
(Lin Yi turned into a wolf)
I've got these huge muscles.
Am I not Xingxu?
Lin Yi.
(Ah)
Did you catch him?
Lin Yi.
(Escaping in the chaos)
(Run)
They took our knife, right?
That won't do.
(Directly taking the woks away)
(Hiding the woks under the table)
Come on.
Are two eggs enough?
(Acting as if nothing's happened)
Where did the woks go?
How come the woks are gone?
The woks.
The woks are gone.
They grabbed the woks?
(Who snatched our woks?)
The woks are gone.
(BA Honglei on the move)
Go ask Naiwen.
(Why ask me?)
(Protecting our woks)
Where are our woks?
(Human shields)
(No one gets past)
Where are the woks?
(Let me do it)
Your combat power is quite low.
Let's cut it out.
Or we'll take your stove.
(Sneaking in)
(Chef Qian knowing nothing)
Don't do that.
What's wrong with you?
(Frantically searching)
You...
So mischievous.
This is ours.
- What do you mean?
- I just poured the oil.
How do you know this is your wok?
Where is our wok?
(I'm here)
Here, two.
Alright.
(Grabbing another bottle of oil)
Where's the other wok?
(You little rascal)
Did you steal one of our woks?
We didn't.
What? No way.
(What I've got is something else)
Why would I steal your wok?
Really.
- No way.
- We didn't.
(Totally kidding)
We didn't steal it.
Impossible.
Why would we steal your wok?
(Someone stole our wok?)
(BA Honglei on the move)
You don't need two woks.
We need them.
I'll take your stove.
(Smug and self-assured)
Go ahead.
If you can stand the heat, just take it.
(Anyway, I didn't take the wok)
(The thief panicking)
That's just how he is when it counts.
Let me tell you.
(Just flip it open)
It's hot.
Honglei.
No.
(We didn't take your wok)
We didn't take your wok.
It's fine, Fei.
Fei.
Why would we steal your wok?
I couldn't have taken your wok.
(Why was the wok there?)
Where would I put it?
Found it.
Grab something on our way out.
(Lei is angry,
and the consequences are serious)
Alright.
Harmony is what matters most.
You know what?
When you're in a bad mood,
the food you make won't taste good.
The thing is, he doesn't cook, Qian.
This is the one thing he does.
(Give it back)
I need to find something else
to cover this awkward-looking helmet.
(Hiding the Helmet)
What are you doing?
Li Naiwen hid my blanket.
Do you really need the blanket?
- Does it actually work?
- Yes.
I have to cover myself
with that blanket.
Really?
Really.
You scared me.
(Creepy, just like an AI)
(Now, the helmet indeed
doesn't stand out)
Everyone's going all out.
What are you doing?
Completing the mission.
What mission?
Are you so cold? Caught a cold?
Yeah, a little bit.
- I haven't recovered from my cold yet.
- I'm cold too.
Can I borrow one of yours?
Okay, here.
He's yanking my clothes off, you know?
(Birds of a feather flock together)
It's too hot.
I've got a light cold.
- Multiple pairs of pants too?
- You've got a heat-induced cold.
Wait.
You've got a heat-induced cold.
Don't yank my pants off.
Only the top?
- I'm a bit...
- I don't believe you.
Wait, these clothes are borrowed.
- I know.
- They're borrowed.
- It's very expensive.
I've got to give it back.
(After snatching yours, go for yours)
Wait, I can't pay it back, you know?
Don't worry. I'll cover for you.
Wait.
Can you believe these people
would be so rude?
Why are there so many flowers?
(Don't see me)
Ignore me.
Mind your business.
(Pulling)
It's too hot.
Lin Yi, no.
Lin Yi, don't do that.
I can't leave this chair.
Garlic?
(What does it mean?)
This isn't a flower.
It's garlic skin.
Mind your own business.
Forget it, Gong Jun.
Right.
Gong Jun, you're so ruthless.
Use Gong Jun's abs
to rub off the garlic skin.
You're very suspicious.
Take another shot over here.
Let's go.
The last one.
(Peace at last)
Come on, I'll help you
finish the second mission.
I'll help you finish the second mission.
Alright, I'm off.
Are you the eagle...
Qian, let's go.
- Is your mission Eagle-chicken Chase?
- ♪For you, I am willing♪
Is your mission Eagle-chicken Chase?
♪For you, I am willing♪
(If you can't beat them, join them)
♪To forget my name♪
Sing it.
Ignore him.
♪Even one more second♪
♪Held in your arms♪
The last segment.
What's the first segment?
He's walking over there.
- Let's walk backward.
- Right.
- That will keep him in the frame.
- Okay.
What are the lines?
(Forced into the frame)
Listen.
Why have you never considered
my feelings?
I won't look at you.
No.
I want to be the one
who takes care of you for life.
(Run away)
Can I?
(Target lost)
You made me wait too long.
Okay.
What are you two doing?
You've never considered my feelings.
Haven't I?
You've never tried to understand me.
Alright, I don't want to argue anymore.
Stop talking.
Am I in the frame?
(That's the point)
This slap is for those three years.
Just go.
(Staying optimistic all alone)
Shoot from a different angle.
Just shoot from a different angle.
(Liu Yuning and Song Qian
have only the final scene left to film)
Let's frame it from far away.
(All passersby are to my advantage)
See, even the lyrics are answering for us.
Every song I sing from now on
will be just for you.
(Completely unaware)
I'll stay with you too.
Just keep peeling.
Just now, Lin Yi and Nai
were whispering.
Seems like they've finished.
Did they finish everything?
Yeah, we need to speed up.
Nai.
It's hot. You'll get heat rash.
It's...
It's summer, kid.
Really.
It's not good for you.
Do it like this.
Like this.
This isn't good.
Let me go.
I'm almost done peeling.
How many are left?
How many...
You need to peel
a few garlic cloves, right?
Right.
(Mission: Peel 20 garlic cloves)
Four, five, six, seven.
Only seven left.
How many cloves do you need to peel?
None of your business.
Give it to me.
Give them back to me, quick.
The garlic-peeling girl is so pitiful.
She even has to wrap herself
in Gong Jun's blanket.
Here.
Thanks.
I've got to take a selfie with it.
You can't be like this.
I'm done.
I can go mess with them now.
Okay.
(Dressed up)
(New outfit)
(Alert)
Don't mind what I'm doing.
Did you steal something?
Okay?
What are you doing?
I'm hungry.
I'm starving.
You are stealing.
I didn't get enough to eat today.
I don't care.
I didn't get enough to eat.
It's okay if you didn't eat enough.
No.
Just let me have some, okay?
Put down the knife first.
We can negotiate.
No.
Wait.
My oysters.
Okay.
Go hide.
Wait.
You eat them.
What is this?
Wait.
Let's go.
This way the oysters won't go bad.
Look how nice I am.
Just stay hungry for a while.
Just stay hungry.
Young people don't mind going hungry.
(The surviving oyster)
One oyster is enough.
Where's my knife?
Xingxu was crying back there just now.
Who? Xingxu?
Why?
I don't know.
He said he felt terrible.
He felt terrible?
Yes.
He ate too many oysters?
Behind the box truck.
He said he felt terrible.
He's been crying there.
Take a look, you guys.
Wait a second.
(Hiding the last oyster)
What are you doing here?
What is that?
A rock.
What are you doing here?
So scary.
What are you doing?
(A sudden return)
That's so scary.
I just want to eat an oyster.
You took my tools...
Well...
Tools?
- Took your oysters away?
- You took all my tools away.
He's...
He's in a tough spot.
He has to first...
No.
Is this your tool?
It's the last one.
Oyster.
Why are you dressed like this?
This is his outfit.
To enjoy oysters is a refined pleasure.
Your...
It's French cuisine.
- Do you need to dress this formally?
- Dress formally for French cuisine.
You've only got one oyster left?
Give it to him. Here.
Will one satisfy you?
Just one...
One is better than none.
Wait.
My...
Ran away.
Where do you think you're going?
Come on. Keep going.
(Exhausted)
So tired.
Mr. Sun, you can take my...
I'll give it to you later, for real.
Let's go.
- I'll give you the tablet.
- Smudge your makeup first.
Okay.
Smudge your makeup first.
Here.
Don't move.
(Makeup recreation accuracy: 80%)
Wait, this won't work.
What if it can't be wiped off?
Can't wipe it off.
Maybe just shave it off.
Shave it off.
Go get some cleansing oil.
(Why provoke him for no reason?)
Let's go.
Lower your head.
(Why didn't you say so earlier?)
(Three main forces going all out)
Are you okay?
Take a breath.
Let's go.
(Gritting teeth and pushing on)
(Let me do it)
(More harm than help)
It's fine.
(Let's go all out and try again)
Three, go.
(Coming to help again)
Go.
(Naiwen's clothes touched it again)
Get her down first.
Put her down.
Put her down first.
(Poor little thing)
Who?
(Security Guard: Wang Yuwen)
Bye-bye.
(Li Naiwen out)
(Lin Yi out)
Bye-bye.
(Guo Jingfei out)
This round, the Security Guard
has unlimited bullets.
(Taking out three players
with unlimited bullets)
(What happened?)
Took out three at once.
Really?
Come here.
(Still can't accept it)
(Obediently follow along)
Wait, wait a moment.
Seriously?
For real?
Get in.
I need to get in too?
Yes.
Hurry up.
Took out three at once.
(Turning around in style)
You got eliminated ages ago, right?
We're all out.
She's hidden us here.
She took us all out.
She might
attack us.
Let's go back-to-back.
- Walk like this.
- Like this.
We look so timid, don't we?
Two against one, yet we're so rattled.
Okay, it's fine.
Come on, get in.
Xingxu.
Nai.
Wen.
Break free from him.
Wait, what about you?
You...
- Played the main villain again.
- Villain.
Wen.
Break free from him.
What about you?
(I became the villain?)
Do I have any lines?
You all have to die today.
I want to blow a fuse.
(Lights out)
Why did the lights go out?
(Where's Wen?)
Xingxu, look.
Wen.
Did you see it?
Break free from him.
What about you?
Let me get dressed first,
and then I'll help you.
Xingxu.
Do you think she will?
Xingxu, think about it.
Just now,
for what you did to me,
I don't blame you.
Was I helping you
throw Yuwen off?
Yes.
You know what to do, right?
Xingxu, hear out my game plan.
Once I button up,
I'll bring your shirt over for you.
Keep Nai held off.
Once you're dressed,
we'll go in together.
This is pretty risky.
Because when you're getting his shirt,
the lights might turn on
and you'll be moving around.
Then you'll have to take your shirt off.
So I suggest you
get in first.
This is pretty risky.
(Lights out)
Xingxu.
Get in quickly.
(Without hesitation)
So touching.
You pounced perfectly.
Right?
Where is she?
Where?
(Lights out)
How did she spot me?
(Protecting)
In the martial world, there's a skill
called "locating by sound".
(Night vision mode)
Are you still buttoning up, Nai?
Nai, are you still buttoning up?
(Only one button left)
Move out of the way.
(Lights out)
I don't want to hurt you, kid.
(How did he get in?)
(I completed the mission)
You didn't button it up.
You buttoned it wrong.
(Buttons all misaligned)
You got all the buttons wrong.
I don't know how to button.
(Only one button left)
He got all the buttons right.
The thing is, you need to unbutton
all of them first.
All wrong.
(Lights out)
Why is it you again?
(Why is it always you?)
Who else could it be?
Hold out a while.
Xingxu will get all buttons done.
Just one left.
(Lights out)
Nai.
(Locked them tight)
Such core strength.
Li Naiwen.
From behind, you look like a giant baby.
(Never Give Up)
(Lights out)
Nai, there's no need for that.
Aren't we doing fine like this?
Let's just take him in with us.
Right.
(Night vision mode)
(Wang Yuwen and Chen Xingxu
completed the mission)
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪That day,
we traveled together far away♪
♪In countless late nights,
we exchanged courage♪
♪Our fates have already intertwined♪
♪In each other's life trajectories♪
♪We leave behind
bonds like no other for a lifetime♪
♪Turns out that meeting you♪
♪Is the joy hidden in the world♪
♪We still have to experience together♪
♪Exploring the novelty of the world♪
♪This is our wonderful encounter♪
♪I find good scenery
for you along the way♪
♪You are the joy hidden in the world♪
♪I'm lucky to have met you♪
♪Traveling around the earth♪
♪Tasting all the freshness♪
♪Having traveled all corners♪
♪We still stand shoulder to shoulder♪
♪I'm glad to have met you♪
♪We sing beautifully together♪
♪Even if we're scattered in the future♪
♪Thankfully we still share the same sky♪